This video introduces 2D and 3D related functions for everyone.
In version 2025.0,
you can set the range of curve and point on the board.
This means that we can make curve and point edits within the range defined on the board outline line or on the internal line.
Now let's see how this function is operated.
Change 2D tool to generate round and smooth curve tool.
And switch to black and white surface.
On the board, click any straight line, curve or line.
Start to edit the range.
Then click another straight line, curve or line.
To end the edit range.
In this operation, a gray reference line will be displayed.
The reference line can be divided into two parts.
The mouse wheel stops on the side to be edited.
The outline line on this side will turn blue.
Click it, it will turn yellow.
Next, we need to decide which line to edit.
There are two options.
One is to click the yellow line on the board outline line or point.
The other is to click the gray reference line.
Next, we first click the yellow line on the board outline.
Then click the yellow line.
Then click the white line.
Click and drag the線 point, straight line or line.
Click and drag the line, straight line or line.
The selection point or line will be edited and moved.
The nearby curve and the straight line will move with the ratio.
When editing the curve, the number of the curve points remains unchanged.
You can also add other points if needed.
If you want to edit one point,
It is possible to press CTRL key to click and drag the curve or straight line points.
One point will be edited and moved.
If you want to edit multiple points,
first press Shift to select multiple curve points or multiple straight lines.
If you want to cancel a certain point,
you can press Shift and then click this point.
This point can be canceled.
Then press Ctrl to click and drag them.
The selected points can be edited and moved.
Sometimes you may want to move the point according to the designated distance.
At this time, you can press and drag the curve point or straight line.
In the dragging process, press the right button.
In the pop-up window, enter the moving distance value.
So we can edit and move the point according to the designated distance.
Next, let's explain how to increase the number of points.
Let's explain how to increase the number of points.
In the dragging process,
if you want to increase more points,
you can press Ctrl and then click on the line section.
You can add a new curve point to the line section.
Please note that when adding points to the Beissel curve,
the curve type will be converted to a sample curve,
and the curve rate may be adjusted due to this conversion.
When adding points to the sample curve,
the curve type is kept as a sample curve.
If you want to delete unnecessary points,
you can right-click on the selected curve point or straight line point,
and select Delete on the menu.
This will delete selected points.
If you want to delete multiple points at a time,
you can press Shift to select multiple curve points or multiple straight lines.
Then right-click on these points,
and select Delete on the menu.
This will delete selected multiple points.
Next, let's explain how to cancel or cancel the editing operation.
In the editing process,
we can press Backspace to gradually cancel the editing operation.
If you want to cancel the entire editing process,
you can press Esc.
Finally, after adjusting,
press the Enter key to complete the editing.
Before pressing the Enter key,
you can continue to edit the curve until you are satisfied.
After pressing the Enter key,
the selection of the outside or inside curve line will be updated according to the latest state after editing.
If you select the reference line at the beginning,
note that the straight line point cannot be edited,
the straight line point will be increased when the start or end point,
and will be updated according to the latest state after editing.
By using this new feature,
we can select a single version.
and edit the range of definition.
The other undefined parts will not be affected.
Therefore, you can only edit the range you need
to improve the accuracy of the version.
Next, I will introduce the optimization of the label.
Now you can proceed to edit the label label,
adjust the direction and color of the label label,
and quickly and clearly visit the label information.
In the 2D window, we have created the label.
Now we need to name the label.
First, select the label label tool in the tool bar in the 2D window.
On the label, left-click to enter the name of the label to create the label.
After entering the name on the label, select Edit View Tools.
Select the label label that has just been added.
In the previous Kolo version,
when the font is reduced,
the view will appear larger.
But now you can manually adjust the font size
to prevent the font from becoming too large.
Come to the property editor and set the font size to 24.
Now there are several font sizes to choose from.
It can make the whole version look more beautiful.
In addition, you can also change the color of the font.
Click on the color block next to the color code.
You can choose the color you like from the color palette.
For example, red.
You can also rotate the label.
Directly stop the mouse at the top of the view.
After changing to double-click, press and hold.
And rotate the label to the desired direction.
Next, I will introduce how to change the direction of the label according to the angle of the number.
Select the label and go to the property editor.
Click on the direction to pull down the menu.
You will find four direction options.
The default angle 0 means that the label will maintain the level.
Angle is 0.
When you modify the rotation in the 2D window, you will use this option.
X-axis means that the label will maintain the level according to the X-axis.
Y-axis means that the label will maintain the vertical line according to the Y-axis.
Parallel to the kill line direction means that the label will show the direction of the kill line.
The update of the label
allows us to add a personalized label mark.
It is more convenient to connect to the subsequent production process.
In the new version, when the label appears in the code,
the warning window will display the label name of the problem.
At the same time, it will be displayed in red on the label.
It is convenient for us to quickly locate the problem.
The label will be corrected in position.
Open the file containing the label information.
Open the label in the object window.
Click on each scale in size.
Check if each scale can be changed normally.
In the process of changing the scale,
if you encounter a scale with the wrong label information,
a warning window will immediately pop up.
The window will display the description of the problem,
as well as the name of the label with the problem.
It makes it easier for us to find the label with the problem and correct it.
When the warning window pops up,
the window size will automatically be set to the appropriate size,
preventing most of the labels from being blocked,
and showing the wrong location with a high amount of red.
The following situations will also have a red prominent hint.
If the distance between the lines is too close, please separate them a little.
If the distance between the lines is too close, please move or delete the point.
The outline of the disc is moving.
The new function has a great effect on increasing the efficiency offish Value Training.
Now, let's apply theORE popularize culture app and modify the base profile to her actual size.
In the 2D window, we can see the decal plates that the cupola has applied the code.
Now we want to apply the code to the tag,
Select the sticker on the application and the board.
After selecting the sticker, come to the property editor.
Roll down.
Find the fixed ratio option, then open it.
Because most stickers need to adjust the size by pressing the fixed width and height.
This will make the sticker search by pressing the fixed ratio when putting the code.
In order to check the results of using the fixed ratio and pressing the ratio to put the code on the sticker,
you need to change its value in the form of a percentage.
Come to the size part and change it from unit to percentage.
Now enter the percentage you need to search in the cross section.
For example, if we have a 100x100mm sticker,
and apply 5% to the X-axis, the Y-axis will also change by proportion.
Increase the X-axis by 5% and add its 5% to the original size.
You can also directly ensure that the sticker is searched by proportion in the properties of the sticker.
In the object window,
select the sticker to be applied.
Under the sticker change information in the property editor,
you will find the fixed ratio option,
and select it to use the function.
When we complete the style design and want to put the code on the sticker,
we can put the code according to the percentage to complete the proportion of the sticker.
The latest function for putting codes on stickers can make it easier for you
to put codes on stickers by pressing the proportion in a faster way.
If the outer outline of the board or the straight line overlaps with the bigger size of the sticker,
now we can use the editor to put the code.
Select the outer outline of the board or the straight line on the line and the curve point to put the code on it.
In the 2D window,
we can see that the board and the bigger sticker form a overlap.
Now we need to select the straight line that overlaps with the sticker.
The straight line is on the outer outline of the board.
Select the tool to put the code.
Click on the straight line.
A spring appears next to the mouse to allow us to select.
In the spring, it will display the name of the board and the name of the sticker.
After selecting the name of the board,
we will select the straight line on the board and then operate it to put the code.
If you want to select the straight line of the inner line of the board to put the code,
it is also the same operation.
In the same way, we can also use the editor to put the code.
Select the curve point on the board and then operate it to put the code.
Next, I will introduce the UI optimization of the editor to put the code.
The push and pull distance and the gap can be displayed at an independent window level.
This allows us to use the editor to put the code.
Let's take a closer look at the push and pull distance and the gap corresponding to the size.
In the 2D window,
use the editor to put the code tool to select the key point of the editor to put the code.
The property editor will display the corresponding push and pull distance and the gap.
Click on the small arrow on the right side of the icon.
It will show the independent window of the editor to put the code.
In this window, the push and pull distance and the gap will be displayed on the same level line.
The value is shown on the list of parkedahahaha.
In this window, the illustration appears that the position of the table is mistakes.
Each sj hoş point in it is assigned to the position of the table in the raise.
Here, I will show you how it should be.
Is it嘇 useful for you?
If you want to appreciate it,
This is also a new feature of the code release function this time.
After changing the push and hold distance in this way,
you can see that the corresponding
axis has also changed accordingly, and the window will always exist when switching other tools.
After finishing the edit, click the close button in the upper right corner of the window.
The window will return to its original state and continue to be displayed in the attribute editor.
The optimization of this UI and the quick way to adjust the value
make the operation experience of editing the code more smooth.
The name display of the horse model has also been optimized in the new version.
In the previous version, the unit machine matched the virtual model.
You can see that because the virtual model name is too long, it will not display completely.
In the new version, the full name of the virtual model will be displayed
under each horse.
When you want to change the horse, you can pull the roll bar below,
or just pull the window wide,
and the function keys on the right side will all be displayed to switch the horse.
In the Kolo 2025.0 version, we updated the Chinese translation of the depth map,
and translated the stress map into a hard map,
and the string map into a hard map.
And this time, the update is related to the depth map.
The depth map is very important in the depth inspection,
used to show the pressure of the virtual model from the clothing.
The new depth map of the 2025.0 version,
through the grid of the virtual model,
instead of the version to calculate the pressure value,
provides a more accurate visualization effect,
and avoids the error of the pressure value and the pressure color,
especially in the case of multi-layer clothing.
In the Kolo 2025.0 version,
we updated the value range of the depth map,
from the previous maximum of 10,000% to the current 5,000%.
According to the experimental data,
when the human body feels the pressure of more than 5,000%,
it will feel very tight and unable to wear it,
and then use the shift key in the upper left corner of the 3D window to start the depth map.
Then simulate the clothing to activate the depth map.
Different from the previous version of the depth map,
the strength of the depth map is reflected on the surface of the virtual model.
Therefore, when you directly click on the surface of the virtual model,
the strength of the pressure will be displayed,
and the area where the clothes are not affected is displayed as 0.
If you want to check the pressure value of the clothing in the area,
click on the Control key on Windows PC and click on Clothes.
As for the display lock added to the mouse light,
you can display the pressure value of the virtual model in the area,
and click on CMD key and click on CMD key on the Mac OS.
In the new 2025.0 version,
if you drag the clothing during the simulation process,
the color of the part of the virtual model will change.
If you want to know the pressure value of the part,
you can stop the simulation and click on the Control key to check.
We hope that the new improvement method can accurately express the pressure area
and improve the accuracy of the version modification,
thereby optimizing your digital clothing design and try-on process.